envita.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy

#### To discuss your treatment options call **1-866-830-4576**

  * 

## Personalized Medicine

A refreshing, new approach to medical care!

View details »

  * 

## Cancer Treatment

Integrative cancer treatment that matters.

View details »

  * 

## Lyme Disease

Learn about our approach to treating chronic Lyme disease complex.

View details »

  * 

## Success Stories

Over a decade of treating thousands of patients and transforming lives!

View details »

  * 

## Envita Articles

Become empowered! Explore our video/article library.

View details »

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

## Do we use cookies?

We do not use cookies.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.envita.com/terms-of-use/

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

### Contact Information

##### Phone

| 

##### Fax

| 

##### Address  
  
---|---|---  
**Toll Free** : 1.866.830.4576  
**Phone** : 602.569.4144 | 602.569.4244 | [8759 E. Bell Road, Building G  
Scottsdale, Arizona 85260](https://maps.google.com/maps?q=envita+medical+center&safe=off&hq=envita+medical+center&radius=15000&t=m&z=16)  
  
  * Home
  * About
    * __The Envita Story
    * __Personalized Medicine
  * Conditions We Treat
    * __Cancer
      * __Chemotherapy
      * __Immunotherapy
      * __Cancer Nutrition
      * __Stage 4 Cancer
        * __Prostate Cancer
        * __Colon Cancer
        * __Breast Cancer
      * __Metastasis
      * __AAIT
    * __Lyme Disease
    * __Chronic Disease
    * __Lupus
    * __Fibromyalgia
    * __Chronic Fatigue Syndrome
  * Education
    * __Cancer Education
    * __Lyme Disease Education
  * Testimonials
  * Contact Us
